A Finding Aid to the Lucy R. Lippard Papers, 1930s-2007, bulk 1960s-1990, in the Archives of American Art AAA.lipplucy
Archives of American Art
- Writings, 1930s-1990s; Series 3; 13.24 Linear feet Boxes 28-41, 51-52, OVs 64-66
  - Writings by Lippard, 1930s-1990s; 3.1
    - Books, Surrealists on Art (1971) (Box 35)
      - Research Material and Notes, 1960s-1980s (Box 35, Folder 32-35)
    - Books, Tony Smith (Art Now) (1972) (Box 35)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 35, Folder 36)
      - Manuscript, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 37)
      - Notes, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
      - Photographs, circa 1966-1969 (Box 36, Folder 4)
        Includes photo of Smith
      - Research Material, Printed Matter, 1960-1980 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Columns (Box 36)
      - D'Ars, "New York Report," Manuscripts, 1965-1969 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - D'Ars, "New York Report," Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - "New York Letter," Manuscripts, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - "New York Letter," Manuscripts, 1965 January-March (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - "New York Letter," Manuscripts, 1965 April-December (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - "New York Letter," Manuscripts, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - "New York Letter," Manuscripts, 1967-1968 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - "New York Letter," Manuscript Fragments, 1960s (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - "Sniper's Nest," Manuscripts, 1990s (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - "Studio International," Manuscripts and Galleys, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - "Studio International," Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - "Studio International," Notes, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Conferences and Symposia (Box 36)
      - Art and Technology Symposium, Rutgers University (1968 May 7), 2 sound tape reels (Box 36, Folder 18)
        Reel 1, side 1 contains slide lecture by Lucy Lippard. Reel 2, both sides, contains lecture by Dan Graham. Note that reel 2 is labeled "Windham Symposium," but as no other reference was found to this term, and both reels are from the same event, this recording has been given the name "Art and technology symposium." Reel 1, side 2 contains apparently unrelated recording, possibly taped off-the-air, of a news program related to the assassination of Rev. Martin Luther King, Jr.
      - Art and Technology Symposium, Rutgers University (1968 May 7), 1 Electronic discs (CD) Research copy (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Art Forum on New Nihilism with Don Flavin, Don Judd and Frank Stella, Moderated by Bruce Glaser, circa 1964 (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - "Art Without Space" Symposium, circa 1960s (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Critica 1: L'Arte da Chi a Chi, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 22-23)
      - Frank Stella and Donald Judd, Discussion Moderated by Bruce Glaser, circa 1960s (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Ian Wilson and Robert Barry on Oral Communication, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - Mapping the Terrain, 1990s (Box 36, Folder 26-27)
      - National Gallery of Canada, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 28-29)
      - Taller Boricua Panel, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - "Time," "Issues in Art" Panel Discussion Series, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - "Time," "Issues in Art" Panel Discussion Series, Forum 2 (1969 March 17), 2 sound tape reels Note on original container reads "Careful when playing, 1st foot or so is twisted" (Box 36, Folder 32)
      - Unidentified Artist Discussion, circa 1960s-circa 1970s; 2 sound tape reels unidentied artists in discussion; labels read "NY 1" and "NY 2." (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Interviews (Box 36)
      - Donald Judd and Bob Mangold, 1965; 2 sound tape reels (Box 36, Folder 34)
      - Donald Judd and Bob Mangold (1965) Duplicate, circa 1990s; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 36, Folder 35)
      - Donald Judd Interviewed by Lippard 1968 April 10 (Box 36, Folder 36-37)
      - Donald Judd Interviewed by Lippard 1968 April 10, Corrected Copy (Box 36, Folder 38-39)
      - Donald Judd Interviewed by Lippard, 1968 June; 1968 April; 2 sound tape reels (Box 36, Folder 40)
        Judd is interviewed in three sessions; at the Whitney Museum, at his studio, and at his home.
      - Donald Judd Recording, circa 1960s; 1 sound tape reels label reads "Judd" (Box 36, Folder 41)
      - Lucy Lippard Interviewed by Lyn Blumenthal and Kate Horsfield for "On Art and Artists Video Data Bank (1979) (Box 36, Folder 42)
      - Lucy Lippard Interviewed by C.A.J. about The Lure of the Local, 1990s (Box 36, Folder 43)
      - Lucy Lippard Interviewed by Scott Marsden (1989) (Box 36, Folder 44)
      - Lucy Lippard Interviewed by Ursula Meyer (1969) (Box 36, Folder 45)
      - Lucy Lippard and Esther Broner Interviewed by Jody Hoy (1989), 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - "'Right Now is Always the Best Age,' Interviews with Women and Girls Age 8-80 on Notions About Youth and Age" by Lippard and Mary Mizenko, circa 1970s (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Sol LeWitt Interviewed by Lippard, circa 1970s (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Tony Smith Interviewed by Lippard, "The New Work: More Points on the Lattice", circa 1970s (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Lectures and Speeches (Box 37)
      - Notes and Texts, 1960s-1970s (Box 37, Folder 5-7)
      - Notes and Texts, 1980s (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Notes and Texts, 1990s (Box 37, Folder 9-12)
      - Notes and Texts, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 37, Folder 13-19)
      - Notes and Texts, Fragments, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 37, Folder 20-24)
      - Notes and Texts, "Gardens: Some Metaphors for Public Art", 1980s (Box 37, Folder 25-26)
      - Notes and Texts, "Headlines, Heartlines, Hardlines: Advocacy Criticism as Activism", 1980s (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Notes and Texts, "Imagine Being Here Now", 1980s (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Notes and Text, Power Lecture for Studio International, circa 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Notes and Texts, "You Don't Know What I Like: The Alienation of the Avant-Garde", circa 1980s (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Questions Addressed to Lippard in Art Schools, 1970s (Box 37, Folder 31-33)
      - Questions Addressed to Lippard in Art Schools, 1970s (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
    - Other Writings (Box 38)
      - "A Note on the Politics and Esthetics of a Woman's Show", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - "After a Fashion: The Group Show and the Critical Intermurals," for Hudson Review, circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - "American Painting, 1945-1965: Cult of the Direct and the Difficult", circa 1960s (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - "Antipodal Anthropolitics", circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - "Art Within the Arctic Circle: A Two-Part Journal", circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - "As Painting is to Sculpture: A Changing Ratio", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - "Back Again", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - "Beauty and the Bureaucracy", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - "Bending", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - "Bibliography of Artists Statements", 1960s (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - "Biting the Hand: Artists and Museums Since 1969" (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - "Bladen: Black Triangle, White Box" for Artforum, 1960s (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - "Brought to Light: Notes on Babies, Veils, War and Flowers", 1990s (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - "Charitible visits by the AWC to Whitney, MOMA, Met.", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Chartres by Auguste Rodin, Translated by Albert Alhadeft and Lucy R. Lippard, 1960s (Box 38, Folder 18-21)
      - "Complexes: Architectural Sculpture as Shelter in Nature", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - "Constellation by Harsh Daylight: The Whitney Annual", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - "Contact Lenses, Corrected Vision", circa 1990s (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - "Contemporary Art in the United States", 1960s (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - "Cross Fires", circa 1980s (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Cuban Book of Essays and Art Criticism, Preface, 1980s (Box 38, Folder 27-28)
      - "David Weinrib (Royal Marks Gallery); Richard Van Buren (Bykert); Charles Ross (Dwan)", circa 1960s (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - "Distancing: Nancy Graves Films", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - "Distant Relations", circa 1980s (Box 38, Folder 31)
      - "Drawing on Strength", circa 1990s (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - "Equal Parts" and "Eros Presumptive", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 33)
      - "Escalation in Washington", 1967 (Box 38, Folder 34)
      - "Escape Attempts", 1995 (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - "Frames of Mind", 1990s (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - Gene Swenson Collection Catalog, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - "Give and Takeout: Toward a Cross-Cultural Consciousness", 1985 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - "The Hand of Memory in Some African American and Latina Art" for Ikon, 1990s (Box 38, Folder 39)
      - "Hanne Darboven: Deep in Numbers", 1973 (Box 38, Folder 40)
      - "Henry Pearson: Black Icons into an Outer Space", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 41)
      - "Heroic Years from Humble Treasures: Notes on African and Modern Art", 1966 (Box 38, Folder 42)
      - "His Eye is Always on the Line" and "Homage to the Square", 1960s (Box 38, Folder 43)
      - "Hot Potatoes: Art and Politics in 1980", 1980s (Box 38, Folder 44)
      - How to '92: Model Actions for a Post-Columbian World, Correspondence, circa 1990s (Box 38, Folder 45)
      - How to '92: Model Actions for a Post-Columbian World, Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 38, Folder 46)
      - How to '92: Model Actions for a Post-Columbian World, Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 47)
      - How to '92: Model Actions for a Post-Columbian World, Notes, 1990s (Box 38, Folder 48)
      - How to '92: Model Actions for a Post-Columbian World, Proofs and Final Publication, 1990s (Box 38, Folder 49)
      - How to '92: Model Actions for a Post-Columbian World, Photographs, 1990s (Box 38, Folder 50)
      - "Inside Picture from the Outside", 1980 (Box 38, Folder 51)
      - "James Rosenquist: Aspects of a Multiple Art" for Artforum, 1960s (Box 38, Folder 52)
      - Kathe Kollwitz, Foreword, 1980s (Box 38, Folder 53-54)
      - "Larry Poons: The Illusion of Disorder", circa 1960s (Box 38, Folder 55)
      - "Lunch 1" and "Lunch 2", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 56)
      - "Lynda Benglis and Adrian Piper", circa 1980s (Box 38, Folder 57)
      - "Made in the USA-Art from Cuba", 1980s (Box 38, Folder 58)
      - Marks in Place: Contemporary Response to Rock Art, Foreword, 1980s (Box 38, Folder 59)
      - "May Steven's Big Daddies", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 60)
      - "Museo, Museas, Museat", circa 1970s (Box 38, Folder 61)
      - "'New' Art as Art History", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - "New York: Information on How to Look", 1960s (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - "Notes in Review of Canadian Artists '68", 1960s (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - "Notes on Max Ernst and a Sculpture of Fantasy", 1966-1967 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - "One Century One Year" for Artforum, 1960s-1970s (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - "Out of Turn", circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - "Parthenogenesis: Giving Birth to American History; Giving Birth to Each Other; Aunt Jemima Meets Barbie and they Fall for Each Other", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - "Passed and Pressing Tensions: Max Ernst in Stockholm", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - "Perverse Perspctives", 1960s (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - "Peter Dean: Builder on the Edge of a Weakening World", circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - "The Pink Glass Swan: Upward and Downward Mobility in the Art world and It's Effect on Women", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - "Points of View: Stuart, DeMott, Jacquette Graves", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - "Pulsa: New Haven/Boston", 1968 (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - "Quite Contrary: Nature and Ritual in Women's Art", 1970s (Box 39, Folder 14-15)
      - "Real Estate and Art (A La Fashion Moda)", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 16)
      - "Ree Morton: At the Still Point of the Turning World", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 17)
      - "Robert Goldwater", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 18)
      - "Rudy Burckhardt: Photos and Paintings, 'The Pursuit of Happiness'", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - "Scattering Selves", 1998 (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - "Sensuous, Sensual, Sexual, and/or Erotic Abstraction", 1975 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - "Sexual Discrimination Against Women Artists (AKA Politics: Art Style)", 1970s (Box 39, Folder 22)
      - "The Silent Art: Monotone Painting" and "Slouching Toward a Decision", circa 1960s (Box 39, Folder 23)
      - "So What's a Wolf Ticket Anyway?" for Artforum, 1980s (Box 39, Folder 24-27)
      - "Sol LeWitt", 1970s (Box 39, Folder 28)
      - "Special Deliverance from the Enigmatic Mr. Johnson", 1990s (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - "Sweeping Exchanges: The Contribution of Feminism to the Art of the 1970s", circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 30)
      - "Ten Frustrations, or Waving and Smiling Across the Great Cultural Abyss," for Artforum, 1980s (Box 39, Folder 31)
      - "10 Structurists in 20 Paragraphs", 1968 (Box 39, Folder 32)
      - "The Third Stream: Constructed Painting and Painted Structures", 1965 (Box 39, Folder 33)
      - "This is Art? The Alienation of the Avant-garde from the Audience," Correspondence and Notes, 1970s (Box 39, Folder 34)
      - "This is Art? The Alienation of the Avant-garde from the Audience," Manuscript Drafts, 1970s (Box 39, Folder 35-37)
      - "This is Art? The Alienation of the Avant-garde from the Audience," Photographs, 1970s (Box 39, Folder 38)
      - "Three Generations of Women: De Kooning's First Retrospective", circa 1960s (Box 39, Folder 39)
      - "To the Third Power: Art and Writing and Social Change", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 40)
      - "Tony Smith: The Ineluctable Modality of the Visible", 1967 (Box 39, Folder 41)
      - "Top to Bottom, Left to Right", 1970s (Box 39, Folder 42)
      - "Toward Total Theatre", 1966 (Box 39, Folder 43)
      - "Trojan Horses: Activist Art and Power", circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 44)
      - "Vancouver Notes", circa 1960s (Box 39, Folder 45)
      - "The Virgin Microbe Comes of Age", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 46)
      - "Visual Art and the Invisible World", 1967 (Box 39, Folder 47)
      - "Women Artists Series: Year Five", circa 1970s (Box 39, Folder 48)
      - "You Are Now in the Middle of a Revisionist History of Net Co.", circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 49)
      - "Yvonne Ranier on Feminism and Her Film" and "Talking, Pictures, Silent words: Yvonne Ranier's Last Two Films", 1970s (Box 39, Folder 50-51)
      - Miscellaneous, Untitled, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 52)
      - Unidentified, Fragments, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 53-55)
    - Notes (Box 39)
      - About Titles, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 56)
      - Daniel Seghers, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 57-58)
      - "Fantastic Landscape", circa 1960s (Box 39, Folder 59)
      - Ideas, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 39, Folder 60)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1960s-circa 1990s (Box 39, Folder 61-62)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1960s-circa 1990s (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1970s (Box 40, Folder 4-5)
      - Miscellaneous, circa 1980s (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, 1990s (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Sandak Slides, Notes and Captions, 1960s (Box 40, Folder 8-11)
    - Oversized Books, Ad Reinhardt housed with Box 29, Folders 11-13, 15, 18 and 23 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Oversized Books, Pop Art housed with Box 34, Folders 15-16 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Other Writings housed with Box 38, Folder 58 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Books, Ad Reinhardt, Research Material housed with Box 29, Folders 14, 16-17, and 22 (Box OV 64)
    - Oversized Books, Eva Hesse housed with Box 30, Folders 21-22, 24-25 (Box OV 65)
    - Oversized Books, Get the Message? housed with Box 31, Folders 9-11 (Box OV 65)
    - Oversized Books, Overlay housed with Box 33, Folders 24-25 (Box OV 65)
    - Oversized Books, Pop Art housed with Box 34, Folder 22 (Box OV 65)
    - Oversized Books, Ad Reinhardt housed with Box 29, Folder 9 (Box OV 66)
    - Oversized Books, Overlay housed with Box 33, Folders 26-27 (Box OV 66)
    - Oversized Books, Six Years housed with Box 35 Folders, 19-22 and 24 (Box OV 66)
    - Oversized Conferences and Symposia housed with Box 36, Folder 24 (Box OV 66)
    - Oversized Notes, Ideas housed with Box 39, Folder 60 (Box OV 66)
    - Oversized Notes, Miscellaneous housed with Box 40, Folders 1-3 (Box OV 66)
  - Writings by Others, 1960s-1990s; 3.2 (Box 40)
    Records are arranged alphabetically by author
    Series includes circa 30 writings by other authors primarily on subjects related to art and culture.
    - Adams, Don and Arlene Goldbard, Picking Up the Pieces: The Transforming Power of Culture, 1986-1987 (Box 40, Folder 12-14)
    - Adams, Gerry, "Culture", 1994 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Ascher, Sheila, "Sheila Ascher's Chronicle," 1976-1977, 1970s-1982 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, circa 1974 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Benavidez, Max, "Chicano Montage: Art and Cultural Crisis", 1994 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Broner, E. M., "Choices", 1979 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Elwood, Sean H., "The New York Art Strike of 1970" (M. A. thesis, Hunter College), 1982 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Flanagan, Fionnula, "Culture Shock", 1990s (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Gibbons, Luke, "Unapproved Roads: Post-Colonialism and Irish Identity", 1990s (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Goldbard, Arlene, "Family Food", circa 1970s (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Hickman, Mary J., "Differences, Boundaries, Community: The Irish in Britain", 1990s (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - King, Susan, "Trading the Maze: An Artists Journey Through Breast Cancer", 1996 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Levine, Les, "The Disposable Transient Environment", circa 1970s (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Martínez, Rubén, "Mexico's Virgin Optimism", circa 1980s (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - McShine, K. L., "Joseph Cornell", 1961 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Medina, Cuauhtémoc, "La Ironia, La Barbane", 1990s (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Melkonian, Neery E., 1988-1990 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Menard, Andrew, "Pluralism/Postmodernism", 1982 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Mesa-Bains, Amalia, "Domesticana: The Sensibility of Chicana Rasquache", circa 1990s (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Mosquera, Gerardo, "El Deseño se Definio en Octobre", circa 1980s (Box 40, Folder 33-35)
    - O'Connor, Garrett, "Recognizing and Healing Malignant Shame: A Satement About the Urgent need for Psychological and Spiritual Recovery from the Effects of Colonialism in Ireland", 1990s (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Somlo, Patty, "Painting Without Brushes: Art and Culture in the New Nicaragua", 1980s (Box 40, Folder 37-38)
    - Spivey, Bob, "Dancing till Dawn: Toward a Social Ecoloy of Art" (M. A. Thesis, Goddard College), circa 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
    - Villoro, Juan, "Mexicamerica Outlaws Border Literature and the Border", 1990s (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified, Article About Mark Bender, circa 1960s-circa 1980s (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified, Comments for the Panel "Between Art World and Mass Media", 1989 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified, "Overdubbing Ireland", 1990s (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified, "Unapproved Roads: Post-Colonialism and Irish Identity", 1990s (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s-circa 1980s (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Oversized Menard, Andrew housed with Box 40, Folder 31 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Teaching Files, 1966-1993; Series 4; 0.76 Linear feet Boxes 41, 52
  Records are arranged alphabetically by name of course location.
  Although Lippard has been a sought-after instructor for workshops and college level courses throughout her career, only a small number of records document these activities. The most detailed concern "Escape Attempts," a course offered several times at the University of Colorado, Boulder.
  Records include administrative correspondence, notes on the content of courses, course readings, and some student work.
  - School of Visual Arts (Box 41)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Notes, 1970s (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Photographs, 1969-1971 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Student Writings, 1970s (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Through the Flower Corp. "Where We Stand" Workshop, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - University of Colorado, Boulder, "Crossing Cultures" Course (Box 41)
    - Notes, circa 1986 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Student Papers, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - University of Colorado, Boulder, "Escape Attempts" Course (Box 41)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Course Readings 1-3, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Course Readings, 4-6, 8, 10-11, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Course Readings, 12-15, 17, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Course Readings, 18-20, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Course Readings, 21-23, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Course Readings, 25-26 and Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - General Notes, circa 1986 (Box 41, Folder 23-24)
    - Notes on "Body, Performance, Concept", 1980s (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Notes on "Fifties", 1980s; 1966 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Notes on "Folk Art/Fantasy", 1980s (Box 41, Folder 27)
      Oversized material housed in Box 52 Folder 2
    - Notes on "Formalization", 1980s (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Notes on "Kitsch and Willow", 1980s (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Notes on "Labor", 1984-1986 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Notes on "Last Day", 1980s (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Notes on "Media and Representation", 1980s (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Notes on "Minimalism", 1980s (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Notes on "Murals", 1980s (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Notes on "Museums and Distribution", 1970s-1980s (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Notes on "Performance", 1980s (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Notes on "Photographs", 1980s (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Notes on "Pop Art", 1980s (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Notes on "Primitive Art", 1980s (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Roster and Student Proposals, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - University of Colorado, Boulder, "Mixing It Up: On Crossing Cultures" Symposium, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - University of Colorado, Boulder, "Women, Arts, and Cross-Cultural Issues" Seminar (Box 41)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 41, Folder 42-43)
    - Notes, 1988-1990 (Box 41, Folder 44)
    - Student Letters, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - University of Oklahoma, Student-Leadership Enrichment Program, Seminar on Multiculturalism, circa 1988-circa 1990 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - University of Queensland, Australia, "Art in a Social Context" Seminar, 1970s-1980s (Box 41, Folder 47-48)
  - Oversized University of Colorado, Boulder, "Escape Attemtps" Course housed with Box 41, Folders 27 and 35 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Exhibitions, 1960s-1990s; Series 5; 4.2 Linear feet Boxes 42-45, 52, OVs 67-68
  Records are arranged alphabetically by name of exhibition.
  Records primarily document Lippard's role as an exhibition curator and organizer with some of her most renowned exhibitions represented here. Of particular note are files concerning her "numbers shows." Files for "557,087" in Seattle, "955,000" in Vancouver, "2,972,453" in Buenos Aires (also titled "Arte Conceptual" in the publicity material from the Centro de Arte y Comunicacíon), and "c. 7500" in Valencia, California, include some of Lippard's questionnaire's completed and returned to her by artists who participated in the exhibitions, specifications for the installation of artwork, checklists, sketches, expense records, floor plans, scattered photographic material (although not of the exhibitions) and printed material. Other files in the series may also contain correspondence and notes, exhibition plans and checklists, research material for catalogs, manuscripts and notes, photographs and publicity material.